

https://www.mayurdiar.com maydiar@gmail.com 🕏

www.linkedin.com/in/mayurdiar in

678.860.0120

ABOUT ME

Forward-thinking UX/UI & Graphic Designer with a certificate in UX/UI from Georgia Institute of Technology, an MBA from Keller Graduate School of Management and a BFA in Graphic Design from The Art Institute of Atlanta, with experience in Adobe CC, Invision, definition & ideation, prototyping and testing, interaction design, branding and HTML/CSS.

EDUCATION

GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

UX/UI Certificate Program Atlanta, GA | 2020

KELLER GRADUATE SCHOOL OF MANAGEMENT

Master of Business Administration -**Business Administration and Management** Atlanta, GA | 2012

THE ART INSTITUTE OF ATLANTA

Bachelor of Fine Arts - Graphic Design Atlanta, GA | 2004

SKILLS + TOOLS

DESIGN SKILLS

User Experience Design User Interface Design Product Design Visual Design Interaction Design Graphic Design Branding + Identity **Typography**

PERSONAL SKILLS

Great Communicator Problem Solver Critical Thinker **Detail-Oriented** Leadership Great Time Management Organized Collaborative

UX METHODS

Research + Analysis **User Personas** Ideation Wireframing Prototyping **Usability Testing Evaluation + Iteration**

TOOLS







WORK EXPERIENCE

EQUIFAX

Lead UX/UI Designer Atlanta, GA | October 2021 - Present

- · Provide leadership, direction and mentorship to a team of UX Designers.
- · Create global consistency in solving user needs and interactions while adhering to brand guidelines.
- · Create wireframes and storyboards of information flow and user journeys that support stakeholder goals.
- Communicate design ideas and prototypes to developers by creating clear functional requirements and design specifications.
- Continuously improve on the global platform through user testing and research.
- Contribute to and uphold the company's Design System to standardize external web facing properties.

CIOX HEALTH

UX Design Engineer

Alpharetta, GA | March 2021 - October 2021

- · Collaborated with team members to analyze and make recommendations to improve current internal and external software and applications and built concepts for future applications.
- · Created low-fidelity sketches and wireframes that represented the proposed value for stakeholders. executives, and end-users.
- Built prototypes to streamline the design development process, test the interface elements, and represent the overall vision.
- · Conducted user testing to identify potential issues and collected feedback for necessary changes.
- Negotiated engineering changes and roadblocks throughout the construction process and offered solutions to challenges discovered on the way.

COX AUTOMOTIVE

Lead UX/UI Digital Media Designer Atlanta, GA | December 2011 - March 2020

- · Created a variety of products, including dataset driven flash ads to complex, user centered UX/UI rich media products for desktop, mobile and tablet.
- Participated in the entire UX process, from concept through completion. Created sketches, wireframes, user flows, low & high-fidelity prototypes and sitemaps.
- Worked with cross-functional groups to maximize new product testing, implementation and troubleshooting.
- Strengthened cross-departmental relationships to identify key growth opportunities within operations.
- · Oversaw training and coaching for all new employees exceeding new hire performance goals by over 20%.